Guide to the Service Bureau, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Service Bureau, Yale University, records
1911-1967
RU 165
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
52.25
(133 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, reports, contracts, inventories, budgets, printed material, ledgers, and building report books concerning the operations of the Yale Service Bureau.
Yale University. Service Bureau
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-F (YRG 5-F), Records documenting operations and administrative services at Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, contracts, inventories, budgets, printed material, ledgers, and building report books concerning the operations of the Yale Service Bureau.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Finance; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Finance; Yale University. Service Bureau
- Records, 1911-1932; Accession 1932-A-009
  - Accounting Department Monthly Cash Report to the Treasurer, 1919 February - 1924 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Billing Record Book, 1925 November - 1932 May (Box 1, Folder 2-5)
  - Ledger, 1918-1925 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tuition, Room Rent, and Sundry Charges, 1911-1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Voucher Record Book, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Inventory, 1918 (Box 3)
    General note
    Folio
  - Ledger, 1918-1919
- Records, 1915-1967; Accession 1969-A-005
  - Accidents, automobile
    - Liability claims, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Reports & blank forms, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Accident prevention & records, 1945-1952 (Box 1, Folder 4-8)
  - Adee Boat House, 1942-1946 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Administration Building, 1927-1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aeromedical Research Unit. Biology Department: Government Contract dismantling, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Air Raid Program
    - Alarm, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - B-20 Budget
      - Bills approved, 1941-1945 (Box 2, Folder 14-20)
      - Budget, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Expense, office and Travel, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Equipment disposal, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Statements, 1941-1944 (Box 3, Folder 24-26)
      - Time distribution, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Blackout
      - Curtains proposed, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Information, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Instructions and reports, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Regulations, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Tests, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 32-50)
    - Bomb Reconnaissance, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 51-52)
    - Camouflage: paint, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Camouflage: school, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Campus Police Reports, 1941-1944 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Certificates and service ribbons: lists, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Chauffeur information, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Civilian Defense
      - Data, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - Headquarters: bulletins, memoranda, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Office, New Haven, 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Coast Guard, additional, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Commerce, U.S. Department of (National Production Authority), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Control Center, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, reports, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 64-66)
    - Data, 1942-1945 (Box 5, Folder 67-72)
    - Daylight Tests, 1942-1944 (Box 5, Folder 73-75)
    - Decontamination, undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Defense Committee Meetings, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Dimout
      - Data, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Campus Police Reports, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 79-80)
      - Curtains and shades, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      - Information, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      - Regulations, revised, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Regulations: War Council Committee, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Violations, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Dining Hall and Woolsey Hall, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Emergency Firemen and phone operators: vacation, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Equipment distribution, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Equipment Prices, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Evacuation Reception Centers, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Farnam, T. W.: Director of Disaster Relief and Air-Raid Precautions, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Fire Crew, Mobile, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - First Aid, 1941-1945 (Box 6, Folder 93-94)
    - Freshman practice Drill, Report on, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Gas and gas masks, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Incidents, reports of, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Information, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 98-100)
    - Insurance, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Journal American: picture story on Yale's civilian Defense Program, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Ledger and remittance, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Mexico, University of, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Miscellaneous, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 105-109)
    - Naval Training Unit V-12, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Occupants, list of: colleges, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Officials: colleges, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Orders, 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Organization, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Pamphlets, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 116-118)
    - Photographic reports, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Picture (sound) machines to rent, undated (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Pipe markings, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Plant protection, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Power House protection, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Practice bombs permit, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Precautions, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 125-126)
    - Priorities, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Protection, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Registration cards, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Reorganization, 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 130-131)
    - Rescue Squad, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Roof watchers, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Sand bags & substitutes, 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Sheffield Scientific School: specifications, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Shelters, 1941-1945 (Box 9, Folder 136-139)
    - Speakers' Bureau, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Spotters, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - Steam valves: Central Plant, undated (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Stirrup pumps: loaned to Yale by Department of Public Works, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Students and Fellows in College Units, lists of, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - Telephones and telephone signals, 1942-1945 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - Tighe, L.G., Chairman: Committee on University Defense: miscellaneous correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 146-147)
    - Trinity College: dim-out, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Undergraduate War Council, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Valve control, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Victory garden plots, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - Volunteers, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - Wardens
      - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 153)
      - Instructions, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 153a)
      - Meetings, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 154)
      - Reports, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 155)
      - School, Hartford Connecticut, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 156)
      - School, New Haven, Connecticut, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 157)
      - School, Yale, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 158)
      - Vacation and Holidays, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 159)
    - Warnings, 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 160)
    - War Production Board 106 contract
      - Atterbury Precast Sectional Housing, 1943-1946 (Box 11, Folder 161)
      - Budget ledger, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 162)
      - Casting Shed and apparatus, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 163)
      - Completed orders, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 164)
      - Inventory, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 164a)
      - Patents report, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 165)
      - Publicity, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 165a)
      - Reports, 1943-1945 (Box 11, Folder 166-167)
      - Requisition #1, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 168)
      - Telephones and office supplies, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 169)
      - Termination, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Warning signals and tests: log sampling, 1942-1943 (Box 11, Folder 170a)
    - White alert: false alarm, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Woodcock, Harold F.: Coordinator, Civil Defense, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 172)
    - Woolsey Hall: blackout regulations, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 173)
    - Yale Community Council, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 173a)
    - Yellow Alert, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Alumni Board, 1937-1939 (Box 12, Folder 175)
  - Analysis: University Bureaus, 1943-1952 (Box 12, Folder 176)
  - Anthropoid Experimental Station, 1929-1931 (Box 12, Folder 177)
  - Architects: Construction Superintendent applications, 1927-1930 (Box 12, Folder 178-180)
  - Automobile application blanks, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 181)
  - Appropriations, additional, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 182)
  - Army basics schedule: classroom and laboratory, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 183)
  - Army: buildings and areas, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - Army: Civil Affairs Training School: room assignments, 1942-1946 (Box 12, Folder 184a)
  - Army Contract information, 1952-1954 (Box 12, Folder 185)
  - Army: data for sketches and photographs, 1927, 1939,undated (Box 12, Folder 186)
  - Army: housing facilities, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 186a)
  - Army: miscellaneous, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 187)
  - Army - Navy: cleaning costs, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 188)
  - Army - Navy: proposed programs, general data, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 189)
  - Army, Navy, Air Corps: deferred maintenance, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 190)
  - Army Air Force
    - Building Reserve, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 191)
    - Buildings, grounds, equipment and instruction at Yale for officer training, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 192)
    - Contract data, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 193)
    - Contract information, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 194)
    - Contract renegociation, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 195)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1945-1952 (Box 13, Folder 196-198)
    - Deferred maintenance, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 199)
    - Dining Hall rehabilitation, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 200)
    - Equipment inventory, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 201)
    - Houses, Lake Place and Temple Street, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 202)
    - Manual, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 203)
    - Miscellaneous: memoranda, correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 204)
    - Occupancy, undated (Box 14, Folder 205)
    - Officers, 1942-1945 (Box 14, Folder 206)
    - Rehabilitation, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 207)
    - Reserve figures, 1942-1944 (Box 14, Folder 208)
    - Robbins, Marcus, assistant Treasurer, 1943-1945 (Box 15, Folder 209)
    - Services and supplies, 1943-1945 (Box 15, Folder 210)
    - Space in Colleges, 1942-1944 (Box 15, Folder 211)
    - Technical Training Command: Preliminary Part II, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 212)
    - Technical Training Command: Routine operation, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 213)
    - Tighe, L.G., Treasurer, Yale, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 214)
  - Army Specialized Training Program
    - Cadet Training, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 215)
    - Campus, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 216)
    - Civilian Affairs Training school, 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 217)
    - Contract, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 218-219)
    - Deffered maintenance, 1933-1946 (Box 15, Folder 219a)
    - Dormitory, Messing and Headquarters facilities: summary, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 220)
    - Dormitory occupancy, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 221)
    - Fire gongs, 1943-1945 (Box 16, Folder 222)
    - Fraternities, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 223)
    - Furniture inventory, 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 224)
    - Medical Program: maintenance, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 225)
    - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945 (Box 16, Folder 225a)
    - Officers, 1943-1945 (Box 16, Folder 226)
    - Proposed program: general data, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 227-227a)
    - Rehabilitation, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 228)
    - Robbins, Marcus, Assistant Treasurer, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 229)
    - Routine, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 230)
    - Schedules, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 230a)
    - Services, 1943-1945 (Box 16, Folder 231)
    - Space, additional, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 232-233)
    - Survey for Dean DeVane, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 234)
    - Termination, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 235)
    - Terms I to VIII, 1943-1946 (Box 17, Folder 236-238)
    - Work data sheets & schedule useable floor area: classrooms (Box 17, Folder 239-240)
    - Work sheets, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 241)
    - Wright Hall, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 242)
  - Art Gallery, 1937-1951 (Box 17, Folder 243-247)
  - Associated Student Agencies, 1934-1939 (Box 17, Folder 248)
  - Atomic Energy Commission: Contract Information, 1952-1954 (Box 17, Folder 249)
  - Audio Visual Program, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 250)
  - Automative equipment (heating), 1935-1936 (Box 17, Folder 251)
  - Bacteriologist, International Conference of, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 252)
  - Berkeley College
    - Architects, 1931-1934 (Box 18, Folder 253-256)
    - Clients, 1931-1936 (Box 18, Folder 257-258)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 259)
    - Contractors, general, 1931-1935 (Box 18, Folder 260-266)
    - Contractors, heating, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 267)
    - Contracts, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 268)
    - Feeders, electrical, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 269)
    - Furnishings and maintenance, 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 270-274)
    - Master's House, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 275)
    - Miscellaneous, 1931-1934 (Box 20, Folder 276-277)
    - Refrigeration, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 278)
  - Berkeley Oval, 1932-1933 (Box 20, Folder 279)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1937-1939 (Box 20, Folder 280)
  - Bids: furniture, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 281)
  - Biology Laboratory: hardware schedule, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 282)
  - Biology Laboratory: preliminary correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 20, Folder 283)
  - Blue Cross - Hospital Plan, 1939-1950 (Box 20, Folder 284)
  - Board of Admission, 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 285)
  - Boardman building basement alterations, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 286)
  - Boardman basement: Fitken future basement, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 287)
  - Bowers Hall (Forestry School addition), 1931-1932 (Box 20, Folder 288-289)
  - Brady, Lauder, Farnham Hall, 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 290)
  - Brady Memorial Laboratories
    - Architects, 1926-1929 (Box 21, Folder 291-294)
    - Catalogs, special equipment, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 295)
    - Clients, 1926-1935 (Box 21, Folder 296-297)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1928-1929 (Box 21, Folder 298)
    - Contractors, general, 1927-1929 (Box 21, Folder 299-300)
    - Contractors, general, 1928-1929 (Box 22, Folder 301)
    - Contractors, heating, 1927-1932 (Box 22, Folder 302)
    - Letters, general, 1926-1930 (Box 22, Folder 303)
    - Miscellaneous, 1926-1929 (Box 22, Folder 304)
    - Telephone Company, Southern New England, 1927-1928 (Box 22, Folder 305)
  - Branford and Saybrook Colleges
    - Alterations: room numbers and furnishings, 1932-1939 (Box 22, Folder 306-307)
    - Architects, 1932-1933 (Box 23, Folder 308-311)
    - Clients, 1932-1936 (Box 23, Folder 312)
    - Contractors, general, 1932-1933 (Box 23, Folder 313-316)
    - Contractors, heating, 1932-1935 (Box 24, Folder 317)
    - Contracts, 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 318)
    - Letters, general, 1933 (Box 24, Folder 319)
    - Miscellaneous, 1931-1935 (Box 24, Folder 320)
    - Refinishing: furniture, 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 321)
    - Refrigeration, 1932-1934 (Box 24, Folder 322)
  - Budget
    - Building, construction, maintenance, 1947-1952 (Box 25, Folder 323-324)
    - Building, construction, maintenance, 1947-1951 (Box 26, Folder 325-333)
    - Building, construction, maintenance: Masters' Houses, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 334)
    - Building, construction, maintenance: Medical School, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 335)
    - Divinity School, 1936-1940 (Box 27, Folder 336)
    - Equipment, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 337)
    - Gymnasium, Payne Whitney, 1933-1944 (Box 27, Folder 338)
    - Law School, 1932-1941 (Box 27, Folder 339)
    - Library, Sterling Memorial, 1936-1941 (Box 27, Folder 340-342)
    - Miscellaneous: expenses & purchases, 1949-1952 (Box 27, Folder 343)
    - Payroll report, weekly: General Managers, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 344)
    - Property and Equipment, 1951-1955 (Box 27, Folder 345)
    - Property and Equipment, 1951-1960 (Box 28, Folder 346-352)
    - Property and Equipment, 1959-1963 (Box 29, Folder 353-361)
    - Property and Equipment, 1963-1967 (Box 30, Folder 362-367)
  - Buildings, College: prints and sketches, undated (Box 30, Folder 368)
  - Building Committee Meetings, 1927-1935 (Box 30, Folder 369-371)
  - Building Inspection Report, 1949-1950 (Box 31, Folder 372)
  - Building regulations, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 373)
  - Building and Maintenance, Bureau of, 1942-1950 (Box 31, Folder 374-375)
  - Bursary students report: landscaping, 1935-1941 (Box 31, Folder 376)
  - Calhoun College: alterations and furnishings, 1932-1939 (Box 31, Folder 377-379)
  - Calhoun College, Quadrangle, Elm & College: Architects, 1932-1933 (Box 31, Folder 380)
  - Campus Police, 1942-1944 (Box 32, Folder 381)
  - Central Power Plant
    - 1915-1917 (Box 32, Folder 382-389)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 33, Folder 390-396)
    - 1918 (Box 34, Folder 397-402)
    - 1919-1924 (Box 35, Folder 403-411)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 36, Folder 412-419)
  - Chairs: orders and repairs, 1934-1939 (Box 36, Folder 420)
  - Chairs: Tablet arm, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 421)
  - Chimney tops, fireplaces, 1933-1935 (Box 36, Folder 422)
  - Classroom buildings and laboratories: estimated income, 1943 (Box 36, Folder 423)
  - Classrooms: special use changes, 1942-1948 (Box 36, Folder 424)
  - Clinic Building
    - Architects, 1929-1931 (Box 37, Folder 425-426)
    - Clients, 1929 (Box 37, Folder 427)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1928-1931 (Box 37, Folder 428)
    - Contractors, general, 1929-1931 (Box 37, Folder 429-431)
    - Contractors, heating, 1929 (Box 37, Folder 432)
    - Engineers, consulting: Boston, 1929-1931 (Box 37, Folder 433)
    - Fitkin basement: 3rd & 4th floor alterations, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 434)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 37, Folder 435-436)
    - Refrigeration, general, 1930-1935 (Box 37, Folder 437)
  - Coal, 1939-1943 (Box 38, Folder 438)
  - Colony and Cloister Club: furniture, 1934-1935 (Box 38, Folder 439)
  - Compensation: Insurance, 1941-1944 (Box 38, Folder 440)
  - Compensation: procedure, 1935-1940 (Box 38, Folder 441)
  - Compensation: special ruling, accident cases, general, 1938-1944 (Box 38, Folder 442)
  - Connecticut Hall, 1938-1942 (Box 38, Folder 443)
  - Construction and Maintenance, 1937-1941 (Box 38, Folder 444)
  - Contracts: government, miscellaneous, 1950-1952 (Box 38, Folder 445)
  - Coxe Cage, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 446)
  - Credit Union, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 447)
  - Crew Shed, 1946-1947 (Box 38, Folder 448)
  - Curtains and shades, 1937-1939 (Box 38, Folder 449)
  - Davenport College: alterations and furnishings, 1933-1939 (Box 39, Folder 450-451)
  - Davenport College, Master's House: furniture, price lists, 1937-1947 (Box 39, Folder 452)
  - Davenport & Pierson College: alterations and furnishings, 1932-1933 (Box 39, Folder 453)
  - Dining Hall equipment: inventories, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 454)
  - Dining Hall: seating capacities and kitchen plans, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 455-457)
  - Divinity School
    - Alterations and furnishings, 1932-1939 (Box 40, Folder 458-460)
    - Architects, 1931-1932 (Box 40, Folder 461-463)
    - Clients, 1931-1933 (Box 40, Folder 464)
    - Contracts, 1932 (Box 40, Folder 465)
    - Contractors, general, 1931-1932 (Box 40, Folder 466-467)
    - Contractors, general, 1932 (Box 41, Folder 468-469)
    - Miscellaneous, 1931-1932 (Box 41, Folder 470-471)
    - Revisions, credits and extras, 1931-1932 (Box 41, Folder 472)
  - Dormitories
    - Beds and mattresses, 1955-1964 (Box 41, Folder 473)
    - Chairs, 1932-1933 (Box 41, Folder 474)
    - Inventory, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 475)
    - Furniture, 1932-1958 (Box 41, Folder 476)
    - Furniture, 1945-1946 (Box 42, Folder 477)
    - Mattresses, covers, pillows, 1957-1961 (Box 42, Folder 478)
  - Draft and manpower problems: general data, 1941-1944 (Box 42, Folder 479)
  - Draft regulations, 1942, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 480-481)
  - Duke University: re: contract, 1954-1955 (Box 42, Folder 482)
  - Timothy Dwight College
    - Alterations and furnishings, 1934-1939 (Box 42, Folder 483-485)
    - Architects, 1934-1935 (Box 42, Folder 486-488)
    - Budget, 1935 (Box 43, Folder 489)
    - Clients, 1934-1937 (Box 43, Folder 490)
    - Contracts, 1934-1935 (Box 43, Folder 491)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1934-1935 (Box 43, Folder 492)
    - Contractors, general, 1934-1935 (Box 43, Folder 493-497)
    - Contractors, heating, 1934 (Box 43, Folder 498)
    - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 43, Folder 499)
    - Refrigeration, 1934-1936 (Box 44, Folder 500)
    - Reports, monthly, 1935-1936 (Box 44, Folder 501)
    - Tunnel Connections, 1934 (Box 44, Folder 502)
  - Educational Buyers' Association, (E.B.A.): Nominating committee, 1947-1948 (Box 44, Folder 503)
  - Jonathan Edwards College
    - Alterations and furnishings, 1934 (Box 44, Folder 504)
    - Architects, 1931-1933 (Box 44, Folder 505-507)
    - Clients, 1931-1941 (Box 44, Folder 508)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 509)
    - Contractors, general, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 510-511)
    - Contractors, general, 1932 (Box 45, Folder 512-514)
    - Contractors, heating, 1931-1932 (Box 45, Folder 515)
    - Contracts, 1931-1932 (Box 45, Folder 516)
    - Kitchen equipment, 1923-1933 (Box 45, Folder 517)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1933 (Box 45, Folder 518-519)
    - Refrigeration, 1932-1933 (Box 45, Folder 520)
  - Electrical data, 1941-1944 (Box 45, Folder 521)
  - Electrical Engineers' licenses: refrigeration, boilers, 1945-1947 (Box 45, Folder 522)
  - Electrical Inspectors, 1944-1947 (Box 45, Folder 523)
  - Elevators
    - Alterations and estimated costs, 1940-1941 (Box 45, Folder 524)
    - Code inspection list, 1939-1941 (Box 45, Folder 525-526)
    - Estimating, design, theory, 1931-1938 (Box 46, Folder 527)
    - Inspection, repairs, 1931-1939 (Box 46, Folder 528)
    - Maintenance and construction, 1936-1946 (Box 46, Folder 529)
    - Maintenance, schedules, 1937-1940 (Box 46, Folder 530)
    - Motors, electrical design, theory, maintenance, undated (Box 46, Folder 531)
    - Records, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 532)
  - Elm Street, 294: heating service, 1931 (Box 46, Folder 533)
  - Elm, York & Park Streets, 1931 (Box 46, Folder 534)
  - Employees: quarterly inventory, 1943-1951 (Box 46, Folder 535)
  - Employees Service Bureau, 1948-1950 (Box 46, Folder 536)
  - Employees: student accident, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 537)
  - Employment: minors, 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 538)
  - Employment regulations: Administrative and Technical staff, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 539)
  - Engineering, planning and estimating: Addenda to tender, 19[illegible]2 (Box 46, Folder 540)
  - Engineering, Science and Management: War Training Program, 1943-1946 (Box 46, Folder 541)
  - Engineer's surplus property, 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder 542)
  - Equipment depreciation, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 543)
  - Faculty Club, 1939 (Box 47, Folder 544)
  - Farnam, Welch, Lawrance Halls: furniture refinishing, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 545)
  - Federal Security Agency, 1950-1951 (Box 47, Folder 546-547)
  - Federal Works Authority: survey, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 548)
  - Fellows, 1937-1939 (Box 47, Folder 549)
  - Fine Arts, Gallery of
    - Addition, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 549a)
    - Architects, 1926-1928 (Box 47, Folder 550-554)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1926-1928 (Box 47, Folder 555)